Xiao Tu
小涂
Is it okay
还好吧
Have taken the medicine
吃过药了
Thank you, Mr. Ji, for your concern
谢谢纪总关心啊
It's okay
没事
Confirm
确定
Didn't see the leader
没看出来领导
I'm quite concerned about Xiao Tu
还挺关心小涂的啊
Care for subordinates
关心下属
It's also the responsibility of the department manager, right?
也是部门经理的职责吧
Hope Xiaoning
希望筱柠
Become a regular as soon as possible
早点转正
Also help us reduce some
也帮我们减轻一些
Performance pressure
业绩压力
Okay
行
Good attitude
心态挺好
Our department
咱们部门
It seems that it's just you and Xiao Tu
好像就你和小涂
Good match for the age of the leader
跟领导年龄般配
Is it right
是吧
Neither is that senior brother
那师哥也不是
Anyone can take a fancy to it
谁都能看得上的
You see
你看
joke
开玩笑
Be jealous
吃醋了
Mom
妈
Don't worry about it
您先别担心
Xiaoning, she may be
筱柠她可能是
I've got some colds
有些感冒了
Discomfort in the throat
嗓子不舒服
I just wanted to ask you
我就是想问问您
When she was sick earlier
她之前生病的时候
What medicine to take
吃什么药
Can you get better faster
能好得快一点啊
Steamed oranges
蒸橙子
It will be fine after eating it for a day
吃上一天就能好
You wait
你等着啊
I'll send it to you when I'm done
我做好了给你送过去
It's okay
没关系
Please don't bother
您别麻烦了
I'll do it
我来就好
That's fine too
那也行
Then I'll send you the recipe
那我把食谱给你发过去
Just do what you do
你照着做就行
Okay
行
That's troublesome, mom
那麻烦妈了
Sir, please pick oranges
先生您挑橙子呀
Right
对
This breed
这个品种
Let's have an activity today
我们今天搞活动
Half price
半价
Buy three catties and get three catties free
买三斤送三斤
Here's some for you
给您来点
Is there anything with better quality
有没有品质更好一点的
Better maybe no activity
更好的可能没有活动呀
It's okay
没关系
That breed over there
那边的那个品种
Directly supplied from place of origin
产地直供的
Extra fresh and sweet
特别鲜甜
Okay
行
Then can you help me with a few
那您帮我来几个
Good
好
Mom's asleep
妈睡了
After taking the medicine, my mother fell asleep
吃了药妈就睡下了
Just in time
时间刚好
It's a coincidence
来得很巧
Mom said you ate this when you were a kid
妈说你小时候吃这个
The cold can heal faster
感冒能好得快一点
Be careful of burning
小心烫
Forget
忘了
But it's also my first time doing it
不过我也是第一次做
Looks like there's too much salt
好像盐放多了
It's okay
没事
Too much salt
盐放多了
Only then can it be effective
才有效果
Really
真的
OK
还行
It's okay
没事
As soon as I walked in the door
我刚一进门
Mom asked me to take my temperature
妈就让我量体温了
No fever
没发烧
That's because my hands are too cold
那是我手太凉了
It's okay
真没事
Don't make such a fuss
不用那么大惊小怪的
Even if it's okay
就算是没事
I can't review any more today either
今天也不能再复习了
Go back early to rest
早点回去休息
Good
好
Is it a little sour
是不是有点酸
It's a little salty
有点咸啊
No
没有
I'll do it for you again
我重新给你做
Don't Don't
不要 不要
I finished this today
我今天把这个吃完了
Tomorrow will definitely be fine
明天肯定就好了
Why don't you eat another one tomorrow morning
明天早上要不再吃一个
Consolidate it
巩固一下
No problem
没问题
I'll make it for you
我给你做
That is
就是
Is it possible
可不可以
Put a little less salt
少放那么一点点的盐
Of course you can
当然可以
Good
好
Sunrise and sunset and starry sky
日出 日落 还有星空
Yes, I think
是我觉得
The most beautiful scenery
最美的风景
Have you with me to feel
有你陪着我一起感受
It's really good
真的很好
What does it feel like
什么感觉
Isn't that
那不就是
The feeling of being in love
恋爱的感觉吗
At that time, you went back to your hometown
那个时候你回老家
I thought you really did
我还以为你真的
Won't come to Star City again
不会再来星城了
I was just thinking
我就想着
Later these romances
以后这些浪漫
But something boring
但又无聊的事
There may really be no one
可能真的没有人
Will accompany me to do it
会陪我去做了
Now I'm back
现在我回来了
I'll be with you all these things from now on
以后这些事我都陪着你
Not leaving
不走了
Tomorrow night is New Year's Day
明晚就是新年啦
New Year
新的一年
I can not be alone again
我又可以不是一个人了
Tomorrow
明天
Let me give you a New Year present
我送你一份新年礼物吧
Really
真的
What is it
什么东西啊
Don't tell me yet
还不告诉我
All right
行吧
How are you doing
你怎么样了呀
I'm listening to you now it seems like
我是听你现在好像
Not coughing much
不怎么咳嗽了
Are you still taking the medicine
药还吃着呢吗
Eating
吃着呢
Three meals a day
一天三顿
Didn't fall behind once
一次都没落下
Let me ask
我来问
Xiaoxiaoning
筱 筱柠啊
There's an exam tomorrow, right
明天要考试是吧
Dad has a good idea
爸爸有个好主意
Otherwise I
我要不然
Go to the door of your bank
去你们银行门口
Pull a banner
拉个横幅
How about fuel you up
给你加油怎么样
Let your mom go too
让你妈也去
Let your mother wear a cheongsam tomorrow
让你妈明天穿个旗袍
This is called a victory
这叫旗开得胜
How about it
怎么样
I'm not going. It's embarrassing. You go
我可不去啊丢人你去
Mom, why don't you give it to my dad
妈 你要不给我爸
Take the whole medicine
整点药吃吃吧
You're right, I'll tell you
你这说对了我跟你讲
Your father doesn't talk about it for a day
你爸是一天不嘚瑟
He feels uncomfortable
他就难受
Let's be serious
咱说认真的啊
Why don't I take tomorrow
要不我明天
I'm wearing a clothes with a hood
我穿个戴头套的衣服啊
I'm pretending to be that now
我扮个那个现在
Fashionable for girls nowadays
现在女孩子流行的
I like to call it
可喜欢的叫
This way this way
这样 这样
What's it called? What's it called, Bell
叫什么什么贝尔
THAT THAT
那个 那个
fox
狐狸
The fox
那个狐狸
I really don't need it, dad
真不用老爸
I know
我知道
You want to give me some relief
你想给我缓解情绪
I'm not nervous at all
我一点都不紧张
Don't worry
不用担心
That's good
那就好
Okay, come on, come on
行 加油 加油啊
Come on
加油啊
Bye
拜拜
I have used
我已经动用了
The power of metaphysics
玄学的力量
I will definitely pass the exam
考试肯定能过
Love you
爱你
Where you are in my heart now
你现在在我心里的位置
Top the list
高居榜首
Individually pinned
单独置顶
Pull it down
拉倒吧
You're on top of your heart
你心里置顶的
It's in the bedroom wardrobe
是在卧室衣柜里
Ji Yuheng who kissed you
和你亲亲的纪昱恒
Since now
既然现在
Already under the same roof
已经在同一屋檐下了
The progress bar can be pulled up
进度条可以拉起来了
No matter how beautiful that face is
那张脸再好看
I have to get off the field and practice it
也得下场实练一下呀
Why is your face so red
怎么脸这么红啊
Couldn't you have a fever again
不会是又发烧了吧
No
没有
It was a cold before
就是之前感冒
Not thoroughly yet
还没有好彻底
Let me see
我看看
This face is not hot either
这脸也不烫啊
It doesn't seem like a fever
不像是发烧
Not a fever
不是发烧
Didn't you say it thoroughly?
就说了没好彻底吗
Just
就
My own body
我自己身体
I know very well
自己了解得很
It's fine if it's not a progress bar
不是进度条就没事
Why are you eavesdropping on people
你怎么还偷听人说话呀
How did I eavesdrop
我怎么偷听了
I walked in generously
我大大方方走进来
Chat with you generously
大大方方跟你聊天
It's you
倒是你啊
With Ling Weiyi
跟凌惟依
Chatting so vigorously
聊得这么起劲
questioning my
质疑我的
No No No
没有 没有 没有
You heard it wrong
你听错了
I'm going to sleep, please go
我要睡觉了你走吧
So suddenly
这么突然
Come out
出来吧
Don't
不要
I have an exam tomorrow
明天还得考试呢
In case it breaks down
万一憋坏了
Blame me if you don't play well tomorrow
明天发挥不好又怪我
Have a good rest
好好休息
Just all the way
刚刚一路
I didn't hear you coughing either
也没听见你咳嗽
It should be almost fine
应该好得差不多了
Remember to drink some water later
一会儿记得还是喝点水
Got it
知道了
I'll pick you up after the exam
考完试我来接你
Booked a restaurant
订了一家餐厅
Eat together
一起吃饭
OK
好啊
I'm leaving
我走了
Come on for the exam
考试加油
Off work
下班了
It's on holiday
放假了
I wish you all a happy New Year's Day holiday
祝大家元旦假期快乐
Get high
嗨起来
Manager Zhao
赵经理
So high
这么嗨呀
Don't go home and stay in a nest during the holiday
放假不回家窝着
Learn from others' young people
学人家年轻人
Go out and spend 80 cents
出去消费块八毛的
This lady
这位女士
I'm now in my capacity as a creditor
我现在以债主的身份
Seriously inform you
严肃地通知你
On January 1st, please
请在一月一号
Before the clock strikes zero o'clock
零点钟声敲响之前
Settle off the interest promised to me
把承诺给我的利息结掉
Otherwise I will put the interest
否则我会把利息
plus principal
加上本金
The power of this rolling profit
这利滚利的威力
You understand
你懂的吧
I'm sorry, Manager Zhao
对不起赵经理
I was a little young and frivolous just now
我刚才有点年少轻狂了
It's okay
没关系
If I guess correctly
我要是没猜错的话
You have eighty cents on you now
你现在身上连八毛钱
Can't even take it out
都拿不出来吧
Manager Rao
饶经理
Are there any activities on New Year's Day
元旦节有活动吗
Yes
有啊
What if you accidentally die
你要是不小心挂了呢
I have an activity
我就有活动了
I can still have a dinner
我还能去吃个席
Celebrate the festival
过节
Don't say such unlucky things
不要说那么晦气的话
If you don't have any activity
你要是没活动的话
I can reluctantly
我可以勉为其难地
Make an appointment with you
约一下你
The right is to help the poor
权当扶贫了
Don't be reluctant
你就别勉为其难
Help me the poor
扶贫我了
I'll put it later
我待会儿把
QR code transferred to you
二维码转给你
You can just transfer the money to me
你给我转账就行
Don't buy that rice flour oil
那个米面油你就别买了
cheap
便宜
And our family doesn't cook
而且我们家不做饭
Is your mouth red
你嘴是抹鹤顶红了吗
arsenic
砒霜
I didn't just have a date with you
我又不只是单约了你
Didn't Xiao Tu just finish the exam
小涂不是刚考完试吗
Let's have a meal together
大家一起吃个饭
It can be regarded as relieving her stress
也算是给她解压了
Not Brother Zhao
不是小赵哥
Did you make an appointment with the leader
那你约领导了吗
Make an appointment
约了
Was rejected by him
被他拒绝了
He said he was going to have dinner with his family
他说他要跟家里人吃饭
Then Manager Zhao is really embarrassed
那赵经理真是不好意思
It seems that our little Tu
我们小涂看来
I have to refuse you, too
也得拒绝你了
People also have to eat with their families
人家也要跟家里人吃饭
And right
还对上了
Make it look like
搞得像
They're like a family
他俩是一家人似的
That
那
scattered
散了
Otherwise
不然呢
Everyone goes back to their homes
各回各家
Everyone looks for their own mother
各找各妈
I'm sorry
不好意思啊
You did it on purpose
你是故意的吧
Driving and wearing high heels
开车还穿高跟鞋
Be careful I'll find the traffic police to report you
小心我找交警举报你
I have flat shoes in my car
我车里边有平底鞋
Thanks goodbye
谢谢 再见
Goodbye Sister Jing
拜拜静姐
Sister Jing, bye
静姐拜拜
Goodbye Brother Zhao
拜拜赵哥
That toe
那个鞋头
trampled flat
踩扁了
Go
去
The restaurant has a nice environment
这家餐厅环境不错
Why didn't Mom follow me
妈怎么没跟着过来啊
Mom's a little tired
妈有点累了
Thinking of taking a rest at night
想着晚上休息一下
I've been hungry all day
都饿了一天了
Take a look
看看
Order your food
点餐吧
This restaurant is a bit expensive
这家餐厅有点贵
It is said that the quality of this place is pretty good
据说这家的品质还不错
But I haven't been here either
但是我也没来过
But just the two of us
但是就咱们两个人
I do think it's a little expensive
我确实觉得有点贵了
Or else
要不
Let's change another one
换一家吧
Let's take a look at the menu first
先看看菜单嘛
It's this time
都这个时间了
A slightly better restaurant
稍微好一点的餐厅
I guess they're all fully booked
估计都已经约满了
If we must go
咱们一定要走的话
Maybe I can only return
可能只能回
The noodle shop at the entrance of the community
小区门口那家面馆了
New Year's Eve
跨年
Go to the noodle shop at the entrance of our community
去咱家小区门口的面馆
It's a little shabby indeed
确实有点寒碜了
Really shabby
确实寒碜
Why don't you try
要不试试
All right
行吧
It's been a year of hard work
辛苦一年了
Think of it as a comfort to us
就当是慰劳我们一下
Not extravagant either
也不算奢侈
Exactly
没错
Hello
您好
Your order has arrived
您这边点的菜到了
Thank you
谢谢
Please use it slowly, you two
两位请慢用
Good
好
I haven't ordered it yet
我还没点呢
The food is coming
菜就上来了
You've already booked it
你早就订好的了
This is after all
这毕竟是
After we were together
我们在一起以后的
First New Year's Eve
第一个跨年夜
It must have a sense of ritual
肯定得有点仪式感
Don't worry
放心吧
Just a candlelight dinner like this
就这么一顿烛光晚餐
Mr. Ji can still afford it
纪先生还是能付得起的
What are you telling me about noodle shops
那还跟我说什么面馆
Really
真是的
Then you invite me to dinner
那你请我吃晚饭
Let me share with you a
我跟你分享一个
Good news
好消息吧
Good
好
I think I did pretty well in the exam
我觉得我考得挺好的
Case analysis
案例分析
After the exam
考完了以后
I reviewed it several times
我复盘了好几回
I think there's absolutely no problem
我觉得绝对没有问题
What's next
接下来呢
What you want to test is
要考的就是
Expand customers independently
独立拓展客户
Then wait for this time
那等这次
After the holiday is over
假期结束以后
I'm about to start looking for clients
我就要开始找客户了
This sounds like a steady one
这听起来似乎是稳了呀
That's even more worthy of celebration
那更值得庆祝了
Thank you, Mr. Ji
谢谢纪总
This Xiaoji
这小纪啊
So thoughtful
太有心了
You see
你看
Ordered so much delicious food
点了这么多好吃的
And brought us over
还把咱们接过来
Really
真的
It's too grand
搞得太隆重了
The child has a heart
孩子有心
Is it a holiday
过节吗
Just an atmosphere
就要个气氛
lively
热闹
Yuheng and Xiaoning
昱恒跟筱柠
After we are together
在一起以后啊
I'm really happy a lot
真的开心了很多
Before
以前呢
I'm because
我因为
Causes of one's own body
自己身体的原因
Chinese New Year and holidays
过年过节
rarely handled
很少操办
The house is always deserted
家里总是冷冷清清的
After that
那以后
If you want to
要是你愿意的话
This is for the Chinese New Year and the holidays
这过年过节的
Let's go together
咱们就一起呗
That's good
那好啊
I haven't been at home for a long time
家里好久没有
It's been so lively
这么热闹过了
Otherwise
要不然
Why don't you move to our house
你搬到我们家去吧
OK
好啊
Then you move to our house
那你搬我们家去
She's got company after that
那以后她就有伴了
Out here
这出去
Take a walk or something
散步遛弯啥的
She wouldn't have to stare at me all day
她就不用整天盯着我了
No, what do you mean
不是你什么意思啊
You don't take a walk with me
你不陪我散步遛弯
Why are you going
你干吗去啊
Find someone to dance
找人跳舞去呀
I I
我 我
This man
这人
I'm going to do something else
我干别的事去
I play chess and fish
我下棋呀钓鱼呀
All right, you
行了吧你
My real in-laws
我真的亲家
I'm serious
我说认真的
Since Xiaoning
自从筱柠啊
After moving out of the house
从家里搬出去之后
Our house is quite deserted, too
我们家也挺冷清的
If you go
你要是去了
Isn't this house bustling
这家里不就热闹了吗
It's too intrusive
太打扰了
How much trouble would that give you
那得给你们添多少麻烦
What's the trouble
这有什么麻烦的呀
But about adding a pair of chopsticks
不过添双筷子的事
Think about it
你想想
Where's the two of us
咱俩呢
You can talk and chat
可以说说话聊聊天
It's okay, let's go shopping
没事咱俩逛逛街
Buy shopping
买买东西
If you decide anyway
你反正要是决定了
Both of us will pick you up immediately
我们俩立马来接你
Right
对
The home is very spacious
家里宽敞得很
accommodate
住得下
Thank you, thank you
谢谢了 谢谢
Think about it
想想啊
This song is pretty nice
这歌挺好听啊
Look at this
你看这
How can we be as handsome as Xiao Ji
哪有咱小纪帅啊
Is it not
是不是
If this time
如果这次
If I go well in the exam
我考试顺利的话
So what's on our VAM agreement
那我们对赌协议上的
Key Performance Indicators
关键绩效指标
Even if I
我就算
It's almost done
差不多完成了
Twenty percent
百分之二十吧
That's going a little fast
那进展有点快啊
What about you
你呢
Tell me
说说吗
The two of us
我们两个
Are friendly competitors
是友好的竞争对手
Why are you still hiding it?
干吗还藏着掖着的呀
Share it with me
跟我分享一下
You wouldn't
你不会
Is it half done already
已经完成了一半了吧
Of course not
当然没有了
Our department
咱们部门
There are only so many customers
客户就那么多
How many more can I hide
我还能私藏几个
Don't let you know
不让你知道吗
Then you are the leader
那你是领导呀
Your secret words
你私藏的话
I don't know
我也不知道呀
There really isn't
确实没有
OK, that's good
好 那就好
Xiaoji
小纪
You have to work hard
你要努力了呀
Good leadership
好的领导
Xiaoning
筱柠
Actually, I'm asking you out today
其实今天约你
Come to this restaurant
来这个餐厅
There's something I want to tell you
是有些事情想要跟你说
You say it first
你先说
It's okay
没事
You answer the phone first
你先接电话
I'll go to the bathroom
我去趟卫生间
Good
好
Hello
喂
Weiyi
惟依
What's wrong
怎么了
Where are you
你在哪儿
I don't know
我也不知道
Qi Yu made an appointment with me
齐郁把我约来了一个
A place I've never been to before
从来没到过的地儿
One of his own hasn't arrived yet
他自己人还没到呢
What about you
你呢
What are you doing
在干吗
Do you want to come with me tonight
晚上要不要跟我一起
Go to New Year's Eve
去跨年啊
The bell tower I heard
钟楼我听说
There are fireworks tonight
今晚上有烟花
No need
不用了
Ji Yuheng and I
我跟纪昱恒
On this side of Wutong Road
在梧桐路这边的
What about eating in a western restaurant
一家西餐厅吃饭呢
We won't watch fireworks together at night
晚上就不一起看烟花了
I heard that restaurant is too expensive
我听说那个餐厅老贵了
He ordered it
他订的
He should be
他应该是
It's been arranged a long time ago
早就安排好了的
What a coincidence
刚刚好巧啊
He was about to follow me
他正要跟我
Say something about it
说点什么事呢
You just called
你正好打电话过来
He doesn't want to confess his love to you, does he
他不会是要跟你表白吧
I won't tell you anymore
我不跟你说了
Come back
回来了
Is it urgent to call you
电话找你有急事吗
It's okay
没事
Nothing happened
没什么事
Good
好
Eat it quickly
快吃吧
What are you gonna tell me
你要跟我说什么呀
Nothing
没什么
Is there enough food
菜够不够
Would you like some more
要不要再点点儿
Come
来
Cut the cake
切蛋糕吧
Are you really
你真的
Don't you have anything to tell me
没有什么话要跟我说吗
Why do you suddenly ask
怎么突然这么问
Come and cut it quickly
来 快切吧
There's really no ring
真没有戒指啊
How about it
怎么样
Is the taste okay
口感还好吗
Delicious
好吃
This is a new store
这可是一家新店
This is from their shop
这是他们店里的
Main flavor
主打的口味
Weiyi
惟依
No flowers
没有花
No cake
没有蛋糕
And no gifts
也没有礼物
So my New Year's surprise
所以我的新年惊喜
What is it
是什么呀
Right now
就是现在
Look
看
It's the setting sun
是落日
Sunrise and setting starry sky
日出 落日 星空
The best thing in the world
世上最美好的东西
It all belongs to you
都属于你
Sunrise and sunset and starry sky
日出 日落 还有星空
It's what I think in this world
是我觉得这个世界上
The most beautiful thing
最美好的东西
He remembers
他还记得
If this moment
要是这一刻
It would be nice to stay forever
能永远停留就好了
Look
看
Here it is again
又有了
Come
来
Here's what we're doing today
这是我们今天
How many times did you watch the sunset?
看的第几次落日
fifth time
第五次
This is the first time in my life
这是我人生中第一次
So seriously
这么认真地
Say goodbye to the sun
和太阳好好告别
Thank you Qi Yu
谢谢你齐郁
Here is what I have received
这是我收到过的
The best gift
最好的礼物
Be careful
小心
Xiaoning
筱柠
Actually, I have a saying
其实我有句话
I want to tell you
想跟你说
No way
不会吧
Now
现在
On the street
大街上
You tell me
你说呀
I want to say
我想说
What happened to my mother
我妈妈的事情
Mom, what's wrong
妈怎么了
Is there anything going on
发生什么事了吗
My dad, he
我爸他
Wasn't he buried in his hometown
不是葬在老家吗
After I came back from abroad
我从国外回来之后
I've never seen him
就一直没有看过他
I'm thinking that after the end of the New Year
我是想过完年之后
Take my mom with me
带着我妈一起
Go see him
去看看他
If you want to
你要是愿意的话
Just come with us
就跟我们一起吧
It doesn't matter if you don't want to
要是不愿意也没关系
Of course I do
我当然愿意了
I accompanied my mother to visit my father
我陪着妈妈去探望爸
This is not
这不是
Is it a normal thing
很正常的一件事情吗
I just didn't expect
我就是没想到
You're gonna tell me this
你会跟我说这些
I thought
我还以为
You
你
With why
以为什么
Nothing
没什么
I'm a little hungry
我 我有点饿了
Me too
我也是
Later
以后
Don't go to such an expensive restaurant
不要去那么贵的餐厅了
And expensive
又贵
The portion of food is small
菜量又少
Come
来
Numbers one hundred to one hundred and twenty
一百至一百二十号的
You can start ordering
可以开始点餐喽
What is your number
你是多少号
Thank you
谢谢
OK thank you
好 谢谢
Come to the menu
来 菜单
Thank you
谢谢
Hello
你好
that
那个
Excuse me, I wanted to ask
不好意思我想问一下
We have all set meals here
咱们这全是套餐
Don't you have a single one
没有单人的吗
Excuse me, ma'am
不好意思啊女士
There are too many people celebrating the holiday today
今天过节人实在太多了
And we prepare the food
而且我们备菜呢
Also according to the set meal
也是按照套餐来的
If you order a la carte
如果你单点的话
Food delivery may be slow
出餐可能会比较慢
Delivering a meal
出餐
Still relatively slow
还比较慢
Right
对
Good
好
It's okay, thank you
没事了谢谢啊
This is the ninety-eight
这才叫到九十八号
We are number two hundred and thirty-one
我们是二百三十一号
How long does this have to wait
这得等到什么时候啊
Just wait a little longer
再等等吧
Haven't you been wanting to eat here for a long time
你不是想吃这家挺久了
Normally we don't have time either
平常我们也没有时间
All right
好吧
I have a number on my side
我这边有一个号
If you two don't mind
如果你们俩不介意的话
You guys take it and use it
你们拿着用吧
Thank you
谢谢
It's okay
谢谢啊
Thank you, thank you
没事
How many numbers
多少号
No. 111
一百一十一号
Akin
阿金
Open up to eat today
今儿敞开吃啊
I got this one half a month in advance
这家我提前半个月
50% discount coupon for the group
团的五折券
Thank you, Lao Zhao
谢谢老赵了
You're polite to me
你还跟我客气
Come
来
Even if no one makes an appointment
就算没人约
It's not like celebrating the New Year's Eve alone, right?
也不至于一个人跨年吧
Today is after we are together
今天是咱俩在一起以后
First New Year's Eve together
第一次一起跨年
Good
好
That's nice
真好
It seems that I remember
好像我印象里
Previous New Year's Eve
之前的跨年
Are you with Ling Weiyi?
你都是跟凌惟依一起吧
Well
嗯
How do you know
你怎么知道的
guessed
猜的
Also
也是
That's too easy to guess
这也太好猜了吧
In addition to spending the New Year's Eve with her
我除了跟她一起跨年
Who else can I follow
还能跟谁呀
But every year
不过每年呢
We both have New Year's Eve
我们俩跨年就是
Get in the holiday spirit
感受一下节日气氛
And nothing else
也没什么别的
When we were in college
我们上大学那会儿呢
The lights in the dormitory went out at ten o'clock
十点钟宿舍就熄灯了
Once
有一次
We'll be back after twelve o'clock
我们十二点钟以后回来
Still
还是
Climbing into the dormitory through the window
爬着窗户进的宿舍
Good thing we're on the second floor
还好我们是二楼
How else do you crawl back
要不然怎么爬回去
What about you
你呢
How do you usually spend New Year's Eve
你一般跨年都怎么跨
I seem to be interested in these New Year's Eve
我好像对这些跨年
Not much concept
没有太多的概念
I remember when I was in college
我记得大学的时候
Every time around New Year's Day
每次元旦前后
It seems that they are busy working on their papers
好像都在忙着搞论文
Later he went abroad
后来出了国
Sharing friends
合租的朋友
They will often be at home
他们经常会在家里
Have a house party
搞家庭派对
But I'm rarely involved
但是我也很少参与
Basically it's all myself
基本上都是自己
It's all alone
都是自己一个人啊
That
那
I'm kind of your first
我算是你第一个
It's officially the person to accompany you for the New Year's Eve
正式陪你跨年的人了呗
You guess
你猜
Does it seem like I'm quite special
看来我还挺特别的吗
What about me
那我呢
Now for you
现在对你来说
Is there something more special
有没有更特别一些
It's almost twelve o'clock
快到十二点了
Why don't you get up
怎么不起来
Come on
来呀
Five
五
Four
四
Three
三
Two
二
One
一
Happy New Year
新年快乐
Mr. Ji
纪先生
I'm the first
我是第一个
Someone who said Happy New Year to you
跟你说新年快乐的人吧
I'm also the first
我也是第一个
Tu Xiaoning
涂筱柠
I like you
我喜欢你
What do you say
你说什么
I said
我说
I like you
我喜欢你
What do you say
你说什么
I didn't hear you
我没听清
I said
我说
I like you
我喜欢你
I heard this time
这次听到了
Happy New Year
新年快乐
I wish you a new year
祝你新的一年
Double the bonus
奖金翻倍
Debt settlement
债务清清
When did you
你什么时候
Started to like my
开始喜欢我的
You want me to
你想让我
Since when
从什么时候开始啊
What kind of words do you call
这叫什么话呀
I also want to
我还想
To make you fall in love with me at first sight
让你对我一见钟情呢
But
不过
It's only four months since love at first sight
一见钟情也才四个月
It didn't take long
也没多久
Who said that
谁说的
We're not
咱们不是
Have you known each other since high school
高中的时候就认识了吗
Forget it in high school
高中的时候就算了吧
If you liked me since high school
你要是从高中就喜欢我
I have been able to endure it until now
一直能忍到现在
Don't confess to me
不跟我表白
That's pretty scary, too
那也挺吓人的
When you first told me
你刚跟我表白的时候
Aren't you very nervous
是不是很紧张呀
Is it so obvious
这么明显吗
What about when I was in school
在上学的时候呢
No matter how important the exam is
遇到再重要的考试
Ji Yuheng, who won't be nervous
都不会紧张的纪昱恒
At work
在工作的时候呢
No matter what happens
无论遇到什么事情
Will be the first time
都会第一时间
Ji Yuheng who tried to solve it
想办法解决的纪昱恒
How could it be
怎么会
Tell me what's wrong
跟我表个白
So nervous
这么紧张呀
Just do what we just said
就按咱们刚才说的就好
You rest first
您先休息
I don't need it for a while
我暂时不需要了
Hiding a ring in a cake
蛋糕里藏戒指这种事情
You must not do it
你可千万不要做啊
What age is this
这都什么年代了
It's too cliche
太俗套了
You tell me
你说呀
This scenario
这个场景
Is it too casual
会不会太随意了
I
我
I want to say
我想说
What happened to my mother
我妈妈的事情
But don't you forget
可是你别忘了
Ji Yuheng
纪昱恒
He also has a lot
他也有很多
Something I'm not good at
不擅长的事
He will be in front of the people he likes
他会在喜欢的人面前
at a loss
手足无措
Will be in the confession
会在告白的时候
Even if you are ready
就算是准备了
A lot of confessions
很多的告白的话
He could only
他也仅仅只能
Say I like you
说出一句我喜欢你
Just one sentence
就这么一句
Actually, I don't know anything
其实我也不是什么都会
Those
那些
A glamorous resume
光鲜的履历
Calmness in front of others
人前的从容
It's all after my hard work
都是我经过努力之后
Just did it
才做到的
Actually, on me
其实我身上
There are also many shortcomings
也有很多的缺点
I hope
我希望
If you see it later
如果你以后看到了
My ordinary
我的那些平凡
Even when it's mediocre
甚至是平庸的时候
Don't be so disappointed with me
可以不要对我那么失望
Don't dislike me either
也不要嫌弃我
How can I dislike you
我怎么会嫌弃你呢
You are Ji Yuheng
你可是纪昱恒啊
You like me
你喜欢我
I'm Ji Yuheng
我才是纪昱恒
If you don't like me
你要是不喜欢我
I'm just an ordinary person
我就是一个普通人
Ji Yuheng
纪昱恒
Always Ji Yuheng
永远是纪昱恒
In my heart
在我心里
Is the best person in the world
是全世界最好的那个人
Hello
喂
How's it going
怎么样啊
Didn't contact me for two days
两天没联系我
In the midst of the dry wood and the raging fire
干柴烈火当中
You did so early in the morning
你大清早的
Can you say something lighter
能不能说点清淡点的呀
How light can the topic of husband and wife be
夫妻话题能有多清淡啊
What nonsense are you talking about
你胡说什么呀
boring
没意思
I haven't had time to tell you
我还没来得及跟你说呢
I'm going to be years ago
我准备年前
Take Qi Yu home
带齐郁回趟家
Pull the progress directly to the end
直接把进度拉到底
What do you mean
什么意思呀
Get married next year
明年结婚啊
So quickly
这么快
Very likely
很有可能吧
We'll get married together then
到时候我们一块结婚
Straight into life
直接迈入人生的
Next Stage
下一个阶段
You want to marry yours
你想结结你的呗
Why are you still holding me
干吗还拉着我
So anxious
这么着急
Marry me off
把我给嫁出去呀
Xiao Tu
小涂
I heard from the guy at the doorman
我听门卫的人说
Achieved results
出成绩了
You check it quickly
你赶紧查一下
I just logged in
我刚登过呀
I passed
我过了
Ling Weiyi I passed
凌惟依我过了
passed
过了
That's great
太好了
Everything comes to him who waits
功夫不负有心人
Okay, Mr. Zheng
好的郑总
When your time is convenient
等您时间方便的时候
Let me talk to you face to face
我当面跟您聊聊
The loan thing
贷款的事
Good
好
Xiao Tang
小唐
Got a new customer again
又有新客户了
Your speed is too fast
你这速度也太快了
That's amazing, isn't it?
太厉害了吧
Development Department
拓展部
Performance is king
业绩为王
I must have worked hard when I first arrived
我刚来肯定要多努力啊
Xiao Tang
小唐
What about this case
那这样的话呢
Brother, I have to say a few words to you
哥就得说你两句啊
What if
如果呢
If I were a girl
我要是女孩
I just choose
我就选择
In the lobby
在大堂
It's stable
它安稳
Of course
当然了
What if you're doing it for Mr. Ji
你要是为了纪总呢
Then I understand
那我就理解了
Li Xiangge
李想哥
You don't know too much
你也太不了解
We're girls
我们女孩了
I'm sure I'm too
我肯定也是
Want to go up
想往上走一走的
And in the development department
而且在拓展部呢
It's also more in line with my career plan
也更符合我的职业规划
The ascending channel is also smoother
上升通道也更顺畅
But what else you're going to say
但是你要说的其他方面
I also have expectations
我也有期待
Tu Xiaoning will definitely do it
涂筱柠一定行
Thank you
谢谢 谢谢
Sister Xiaoning
那筱柠姐
Congratulations
恭喜你呀
I didn't expect it to be so soon
没想到这么快
Just passed the written test
就通过笔试了
What's unexpected about this
这有什么没想到的
I already guessed Xiao Tu
我早就猜到小涂
It will definitely pass in one go
一定能一次通过
We expand the future of our department
我们拓展部未来
There must be a place for you
必有你一席之地
Thank you, Brother Zhao
谢谢小赵哥
You're welcome
不客气
A long way to go
任重道远
There's still a lot of hurdles to pass ahead
后面还有好多关要过呢
Xiao Tu ah
小涂啊
We can't just have a long way to go
咱们不能只任重道远
Is it right
是吧
We have to race against time in the future
咱未来得争分夺秒
What about the quota of labor dispatch to become full-time
劳务派遣转正名额呢
Very little
非常的少
You passed the written test
你过了笔试
Just basic conditions
只是基础条件
But we need sufficient conditions
但是咱们需要充分条件
You have to do it in the shortest possible time
你要在最短的时间内
Raise your performance
把自己的业绩提上来
Prove that we
证明咱们
Worthy of this spot
配得上这个名额
Talk about it
说来说去
Isn't it just developing customers
不就是开发客户吗
That's right
说得没错
Sister Xiaoning
那筱柠姐
You need to hold on tighter
你可得抓点紧了
From developing customers to lending
从开发客户到放款
And one more
还有一个
A very long process
非常漫长的过程
Everyone, hurry up, hurry up
各位 快 快 快
It's zero o'clock soon
马上零点了
Now go to the playground
现在去操场
Still in time for the countdown to the New Year
还赶得上新年倒计时
Yuheng
昱恒
Let's go together
一块去呗
There are a lot of girls in the school next door
隔壁校好多女生
Let's all come to celebrate the New Year's Eve together
都过来一块跨年呢
I won't go
我就不去了
You guys go quickly
你们快去吧
If you are a master of learning, give it to yourself
学霸就给自己
Take a day off
放一天假吗
Is it not
是不是
Today's size is considered a holiday
今天大小也算个节日啊
Yeah, yeah
对啊
Brothers, you go first
哥几个你们先去吧
Okay, let's go first
行那我们先去吧
We can't catch up
咱赶不上了
Hurry, hurry, hurry
快 快 快
New Year
新的一年
Who's the first one to tell you
谁是第一个跟你说
Happy New Year people
新年快乐的人呢
Happy New Year
新年快乐
Tu Xiaoning
涂筱柠